Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
[Whispers of Fate]
[Episode 35]
Mother...
The Thousand-Armed and Thousand-Eyed
Unhindered Great Compassion Dharani.
What they're doing
won't help with anything.
There isn't much time left.
I'll have to use
the Heaven-Halo Technique.
The Rebirth Scroll?
Such pure power,
plus that armor...
He's the Holy Son!
Now that you've recognized me,
why not step back?
Only I can save her life.
Heaven Halo, activate!
It's the Heaven-Halo Technique!
Retreat!
Quickly inform the Asura King
of Lord Ye Mo's return!
The Goddess will be saved!
The Heaven-Changing Scripture?
Didn't expect that, did you?
As the Holy Son of Tianren Realm,
you have infinite power.
Your body
is perfect for me.
Why give it away to Yique Yinyang
for nothing?
Since the beginning,
you've been calculating.
If I had mistakenly killed the Goddess,
I wouldn't have been born,
and Yique Yinyang couldn't be revived.
Then you could continue being yourself.
Correct.
If I didn't kill her,
you'd use the Heaven-Changing Scripture
to disrupt her meridians.
In order to save her,
I'd definitely activate the Heaven Halo,
presenting you a chance
to possess my body.
That's right.
Knowing that I'd regain my power
in Tianren Realm,
you had me inhale the toxic air
given out
by the plants in the Plum Garden,
so as to suppress my power.
Given that,
even in Tianren Realm,
the strike I just launched
wouldn't be able to kill you.
Tang Lici,
you
have
lost.
Nonetheless,
I still need to thank you.
If it hadn't been for you,
I would never have known
that my mother
has always loved me.
A Holy Son of Tianren Realm
with all sorts of emotions...
What a perfect Tianren body.
It's finally going to be mine.
When we become one,
we'll form
a new Yique Yinyang.
Heaven-Changing Scripture,
reverse the Heaven Halo.
Under no circumstances
will Tang Lici turn into Yique Yinyang!
I'm the son of the Dragon Goddess
and the real Tianren.
♪ Vast lands ♪
Ghostly Peony,
♪ And boundless skies ♪
you placed bets on me killing my mother
in a vain attempt
to make me use the Heaven-Halo Technique,
♪ The world is in turmoil ♪
so as to possess my body.
♪ Storms are rising ♪
You've truly angered me.
You've got your power back?
♪ Heroes stand proud ♪
Yes.
Now, I have a complete Tianren body.
♪ Their will is like steel ♪
You can't take it from me.
Don't you yearn to have
human emotions?
♪ Through storm and frost,
the swords they wield ♪
♪ Cutting down all evil
between heaven and earth ♪
I'll make that
come true for you.
♪ Flames of war sweep across the world ♪
♪ Good has not yet triumphed over evil ♪
♪ The moon in the water ♪
Heaven Halo, activate.
♪ Holds lost dreams ♪
♪ The world's at the fingertips ♪
♪ Hidden within a warrior's heart ♪
Believe in yourself.
♪ The endless seas and lands ♪
You won't hurt it.
♪ Await my burning passion ♪
Killing is in your nature.
You have an innate urge for blood.
I'm not Tang Lici at all!
Nor do I belong to Zhoudi Tower!
♪ Facing swords and blades, I roar alone ♪
Let go!
♪ With supreme power,
I roam free under heaven ♪
You monster.
♪ Mad and laughing
like Buddha or a demon ♪
But your golden eyes and forehead mark
look pretty nice.
♪ A roar, and winds and clouds howl ♪
Today,
with me here, you won't get to him!
♪ Behold the land, miles wide ♪
There was no other reason.
I just wanted to save you.
♪ Where rolling waves surge ♪
Save your compassion.
I am a monster.
♪ Facing swords and blades, I roar alone ♪
I was created with the purpose
to kill.
But you care about Chi Yun
and everyone else, including me.
♪ With supreme power,
I roam free under heaven ♪
But Fang Zhou never taught me
how to love someone.
♪ Mad and laughing
like Buddha or a demon ♪
♪ A roar, and winds and clouds howl ♪
♪ No madness, no fire ♪
♪ How can one be called a hero? ♪
Now I know what it is like
to have feelings.
You finally woke up.
You look
exactly
like I imagined.
Remember:
Mother
loves you.
Mother.
The notorious Sky-reaching Pillar
shouldn't exist at all.
Dragon fire, burn the non-heavenly titan!
Yique Yinyang,
the bronze tree has been destroyed.
How are you going to come back to life?
Son,
take a look at the starry sky
outside for me.
Remember:
Mother
loves you.
Mother...
I predicted
that you'd win this battle.
But, Mr. Tang, you didn't predict
that I'd leave without saying goodbye.
Ghostly Peony attempted to use a puppet
and the power of the bronze tree
to guide Yique Yinyang back to life.
I hid the third pill, the real one,
from everyone.
I then merged
the Sky-Fallen Stone fragment in me
with the pill.
This time,
I've finally
thought one step ahead of you.
I recalled my real name
and found out where I'm from.
I also misunderstood
and lied to you.
I can't face you again.
I just hope that after I leave,
you'll no longer fear
being understood by others.
You hate to explain yourself.
You don't care if others understand you
or trust you.
You don't mind even if everyone
misunderstands you.
I used to think of it
as arrogance.
Only some time later did I realize
that you were just afraid.
You feared
that you didn't deserve to be understood
or trusted.
Being understood isn't a bad thing.
This is the last time
I offer you my advice.
At the end of the road,
it's better to let go of the past.
Mr. Tang,
let's stay out of each other's life
for good.
Okay.
Shei, just go to a place
where Tang Lici isn't there.
Lead a life of your choice.
News of victory!
Tang Lici, the Guest of Honor
of the Central Plains Sword Alliance,
ventured alone into enemy lines
to destroy Fengliu Shop at one fell swoop,
and eliminated the mastermind,
Ghostly Peony!
Everyone in Shenji Branch,
did you see it?
When the bronze tree collapsed,
the earth split, mountains crumbled,
and flames went everywhere!
First, Xiuyu Peony Pavilion fell.
Then, the Plum Garden was flattened.
The enemy's base and final stronghold
were taken down by us once at a time.
Fengliu Shop
will never stand a chance to rise again!
Bravo!
Victory is finally ours
after such a long time!
How satisfying!
It's good to take an optimistic attitude.
However...
has Shenji Branch
found any trails of Mr. Tang
and Mr. Chi,
who went to look for the former?
Well...
Given the complex terrain
of Puti Valley,
and that we are remotely
stationed this time,
we can only figure out
their general movements.
With luck, they'll be able
to escape before the mountain collapses.
But without luck...
Stop picturing the worst case scenario.
I just...
People are finally having a chance
to take a breather now.
In my opinion,
we should delay announcing
Mr. Tang's disappearance.
[Half a month later]
One.
Two.
Everyone, look sharp!
Just because we've won doesn't mean
we can slack off.
Some members
of Fengliu Shop are still at large.
It depends on you to maintain
the order
of the future martial arts world.
Your Highness.
Dismissed.
I, Gu Xitan, am glad
to meet Your Highness.
Where is my master?
Where is he?
Master Shao is in Qingyang Realm.
Your Highness!
May I ask
if you were conscious
when you stabbed Mr. Tang?
Will you believe me?
I'd love to, if I can,
Ms. Zhong.
Master, after you entrusted
the Sword Alliance to my care,
I spent 10 years fixing
the damage caused by Yique Yinyang,
and 10 years elevating my spirit
as I longed for jianghu
to be reshaped by drastic measures.
I have waited 10 years
for the game changer.
Master,
why are you here alone?
I...
I'm admiring the scenery of Mount Cloud.
I used to be so busy with the affairs
of the Sword Alliance
that I never knew
there was such beautiful scenery here.
People can't see
what they normally can't
until they take a pause
from hustle and bustle.
I heard...
that Chi Yun and Shen
went to look for Mr. Tang.
I'm talking about Mr. Tang.
Master!
Senior,
what happened to my master?
He worked himself into illness,
which has already taken a toll
on his health.
Then, during the battle on Mount Cloud,
he suffered severe internal injuries.
Instead of working again,
he should've taken a rest.
Now, his heart
and meridians have been harmed.
At this rate,
you'll even die before Tang Lici does.
Is it really that serious?
It seems I've discovered more than
the scenery of Mount Cloud
during this pause from work.
Master,
please listen to Senior.
Master Shao.
Look at you.
You haven't recovered yet.
Why come here
to join the crowd?
At least I can still stand on my feet.
All I suffered
was a tiny little injury.
This "tiny little injury"
nearly killed you.
It hasn't healed after half a month.
Fengliu Shop has been taken down already.
God knows what you are
still busy with every day.
There's something I have to say.
Senior Shui...
Miss Shui,
Chunji,
I'd like to have a word with Master Cheng
and Master Puzhu in private.
Master Shao is inviting all the elders
and Branch Chiefs of the Sword Alliance
to Qingyang Realm for a discussion
on an important issue.
Today, I gathered all of you here
to make an announcement.
What happened?
I've decided
to step down as Sword Master
of the Central Plains Sword Alliance.
Though Fengliu Shop has been crushed,
its members at large
might cause turbulence again.
Tough measures must be taken promptly
to root out all the evil.
My frail body can no longer
bear heavy responsibilities.
It is high time
you elected a new leader.
Master Shao,
the Sword Alliance
still needs your leadership.
Please reconsider.
Master Shao, please reconsider.
Please reconsider!
Don't worry, everyone.
I've consulted Master Puzhu
and Master Cheng.
In the next two months,
Master Cheng will be
the acting Sword Master.
There's still time
before the election begins,
which allows us to deliberate.
Master Shao, do you
have anyone in mind as your successor?
None of the former Sword Masters
were appointed by their predecessors.
They were nominated
by senior members such as yourselves.
Master Shao,
does everyone get to make a nomination?
Of course.
Anyone can
be nominated.
The key is
to gain the approval and recognition
of the alliance and everyone.
That said,
a proven record of upholding justice
in the martial world
would be a significant advantage.
Master Shao,
I'd like to nominate...
myself.
What?
Miss Xifang,
you've just joined the Sword Alliance...
Indeed, I'm new here
and still familiarizing myself
with the Sword Alliance.
May I ask, Master Shao,
if seniority is a must for those running
for the position of Sword Master?
As far as I know,
Mr. Tang didn't join the Sword Alliance
much earlier than I did.
Is Mr. Tang,
who has rendered monumental service
to the alliance,
also not qualified
to run for the position of Sword Master?
Since you know little
about the Sword Alliance,
why boldly engage yourself
in the election?
I don't know much now,
but it doesn't mean
I'd stay that way forever.
Besides, I'm also
a member of the Sword Alliance now.
Seniority is not a must for those
running for the position of Sword Master.
But the approval of all the masters
and disciples is still necessary.
Thank you, Master Shao.
All I need to know
is that I'm qualified
to run for the position of Sword Master.
As for gaining people's approval...
that's my own concern.
Miss Xifang,
since you joined the Sword Alliance,
you've appeared eager and ambitious.
You and I are merely
acquaintances.
Master Puzhu,
as her referee,
what's your opinion?
It's unnecessary
to trouble Master Puzhu
with my own business.
Master Puzhu
is simply a guide for me.
The path I'll walk in the Sword Alliance
doesn't necessarily
have to be decided by Master Puzhu.
I know
that you, Master Shao,
and Master Cheng have doubts.
Since I used to work for Fengliu Shop,
your concerns are understandable.
Let me just point out two things.
First,
among all the people present
except Master Cheng
and Master Puzhu,
I am the best martial fighter here.
Second,
though Fengliu Shop has been defeated,
its remaining power
could still be a threat.
Nobody knows
Fengliu Shop better than I do.
Therefore,
before Fengliu Shop is annihilated,
I'm most suited for the position
of Sword Master, temporarily.
Temporarily?
What do you mean?
I hereby swear to all of you...
Within half a year,
I'll root out Fengliu Shop.
Well...
After that,
I'm willing to step down,
so the Sword Alliance
can elect a new Sword Master.
Why?
Miss Xifang, are you planning
to fulfill
some sort of wish in half a year?
I'm aware of the grave sins
I've committed.
Running for the position of Sword Master
is never my intention,
but I have no other choice.
If I am to atone for my sins,
my only option is to eradicate
Fengliu Shop.
In that case,
Miss Xifang,
why apply to be Sword Master?
Just lead from the front
when we attack Fengliu Shop.
Won't that be enough?
Everyone,
I also think I'm qualified
to run for the position of Sword Master.
Well...
Your Highness,
leading the Sword Alliance
is by no means an easy task.
Of course,
I'm not looking down
on Your Highness's capabilities.
But even Master Puzhu
and Master Cheng
show no interest in this position.
So, you see...
Ms. Zhong,
I suggest you just be content
with your position as a royal princess.
But, I...
am my Master's only disciple
and the chief of Shanfeng Branch.
Since the age of eight,
I've been observing how Master
manages the Sword Alliance
by his side every day.
I've handled more alliance affairs
than the fellow martial practitioners
you killed
when you worked for Fengliu Shop.
Miss Xifang,
as a newcomer
who was an outsider not long ago,
you have the nerve to enter the election.
How am I, the chief of Shanfeng Branch,
the least qualified
candidate for the post?
It seems Your Highness has quickly
got tired of being a princess.
Master Shao.
Mr. Tang is back!
Mr. Tang?
I wonder
if I'm qualified for the election.
Mr. Tang,
you finally came back.
Your injuries...
I'm fine.
I have fully recovered.
However...
You don't seem well,
Master Shao.
I venture to compete
for the position
of the Sword Alliance's Sword Master.
I hope to have
your support.
When I saw Mr. Tang,
my body was out of control,
and I stabbed him.
Your Highness,
will you withdraw from the election?
At the moment,
Master needs a good rest.
I'm afraid the successor he deems suitable
may not be me.
It's also my belief
that after making so many contributions,
it's time for Master Shao to recuperate,
since the battle is over now.
But Your Highness is indeed
more familiar with the alliance affairs
than others.
Mr. Tang's sudden return
may not be good news
to Your Highness.
Your Highness comes from jianghu
and values loyalty.
It's admirable.
But the old days have passed.
Now,
Your Highness is the Emperor's daughter.
That means
Your Highness can't act like
someone in jianghu anymore,
especially not
be too emotionally involved.
That won't bring
anything good
to Your Highness or the court.
Are you suggesting
I go against my Master's will
and replace him?
I dare not.
Without Master's guidance,
I wouldn't have become who I am today.
I don't allow anyone to be disrespectful
to my Master.
I've overstepped my bounds.
I beg for Your Highness's forgiveness.
But has Your Highness thought about this?
Now, Fengliu Shop has fallen.
The future martial arts world
needs a Sword Master
who's adept in governance
and the art of balance.
Your Highness is a member of the court
and Master Shao's direct disciple.
Your Highness has great respect
and care for Master Zhao,
and thus won't be a threat to him.
But will others in the Sword Alliance
still be bound to Master Shao
by the ties of discipleship
just like Your Highness?
You're referring to...
Xifang Tao?
Xifang Tao acts flamboyantly
and curries favor everywhere.
Mr. Tang always takes radical action,
and on top of that,
he has been wounded by Your Highness.
At the moment, Master Shao is unwell.
I'm afraid the rivalry
between Mr. Tang and Xifang Tao
will plunge the alliance
into a new crisis,
and that Your Highness
will lose your foothold.
Neither Master Shao nor the Emperor
would like to see that happen.
Your Highness,
that suggestion of mine
is not only for your own good,
but also for the interest
of the entire jianghu
and your master's life's work.
I get it.
You may leave.
Senior!
I see you're back.
Now that Fengliu Shop has collapsed,
you won't have to tire yourself out
anymore.
From now on,
come here more often.
I'll make sure you get well.
Take a seat over there.
I'll check your pulse later
to see how you've been.
I'm not ill.
Only the doctor has the final say.
You already got your martial strength
back.
But since your power and blood
have been depleted,
and your inner energy disrupted,
you won't be able to heal
as fast and easily as before.
These days,
you must refrain from losing blood
and using the Rebirth Scroll again
to save lives.
Those three pills have been used up.
Your current condition is far more
dangerous than you imagine.
One reckless move could cost your life.
Senior,
if anyone asks,
can you reply
with the first sentence only?
Senior.
Now, the Sword Alliance
needs
a Tang Lici in his prime.
And my companions
also need that.
So,
please do me a favor.
Does Shei still count
as a companion of yours?
Master.
Are you alright?
Hearing about your return,
he insisted on visiting you.
I couldn't stop him at all.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
How's your health?
He has regained his martial strength.
Anything else?
He's fine. Just leave.
All this noise is giving me a headache.
Thank you, Senior.
Let's go.
Shei...
is gone.
Miss Shei
already left.
When will she...
come back?
She won't be back anymore.
Master, you're lying.
Shei likes you a lot.
She'll definitely come back.
Anything you want to say to me, Shen?
Chi Yun went to look for you.
I asked him to send me messages,
but I haven't heard from him so far.
How long has he been gone?
More than half a month.
There's one more thing.
I received a message from Chief,
saying that he had
found the last jewel
of the Seven-Treasure Jade Hairpin,
and that I should go back
to Shisan Tower instantly.
If I arrive before the deadline,
he'll return Huiniang's body to me.
If not,
he'll consider it a breach of agreement
and destroy Huiniang's body.
When's the deadline he gave you?
Tomorrow noon.
This matter can't wait.
Shen,
set off today.
But what about Chi Yun?
I'm here now.
How are you still worried?
I'm not.
Goodbye.
No need to see me off.
Bye.
Master,
why are there...
less and less people around?
People...
are born to be
separate individuals.
No.
I'll always be with you, Master.
Sure.
I asked to meet you for an inquiry.
Do you know
where the Plum Garden is?
[Half a month ago]
It has been destroyed.
Tang Lici is fine now.
You can go now.
Miss Bai...
I don't know
what secrets you're keeping from me.
But I know you're a good person.
Chi Yun,
stop waiting for me.
Miss Bai...
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have bothered you
with my unrequited feelings.
[Marriage Agreement]
Your father arranged a marriage for us.
I've been carrying this agreement with me.
I've finally realized how foolish I was
for thinking I could marry you
based on this mere sheet of paper.
I've burned the marriage agreement now.
It's officially void.
I, Chi Yun,
swear to make you gladly marry me
one day.
If I can't marry you,
I won't marry anyone else.
Whatever.
It's your own business.
Besides,
I have my own matters to attend to.
She came here alone.
Did Fengliu Shop force her
to do something?
That's bad. I must follow her.
[Tingyun Pavilion]
Come on.
Try the newly harvested tea of this year.
Rich aroma.
Sweet aftertaste.
It's a fine product from Camellia Island.
Does Master Cheng
know you took his tea leaves?
He won't,
if nobody tells him.
Now that you've drunk it,
we are
on the same boat.
I'm afraid this boat
has been infiltrated by the crooked.
What's worse,
it's about to capsize.
Someone ill-intentioned
has sneaked onto this boat.
Recently,
Xifang Tao has done
much work for the Sword Alliance.
Externally,
she publicly offers rewards
for Liu Yan's capture,
and relentlessly hunts after
the remaining members of Fengliu Shop.
Her reputation has quickly soared.
Now, in people's eyes,
she's a pioneer in eliminating the evil.
Internally,
she cares for those
who were wounded in the battle,
and patiently offers instructions
to the new disciples
of the Sword Alliance.
The last time I met her,
she was chief
of the West Palace in Fengliu Shop.
In just a bit over a month,
she has somehow become
a revered heroine of justice.
It's hard to discern
the true nature of those of her kind—
I mean people who are skilled
in ingratiating themselves with others.
Master Shao, are you worried
that she may have ulterior motives?
As for Mr. Chi...
why don't I issue a missing person notice
in the name of the Sword Alliance?
I'd hate to trouble the alliance now.
At the moment, our priority
is to stop the spread
of the Blood Ghost Pills.
Speaking of which,
given
that we've devastated the Sword King City,
which was the major route
for selling poison pills
on land and by water,
and that we've destroyed
Xiuyu Peony Pavilion
and the Plum Garden,
there should be less and less
Blood Ghost Pills.
Why has there been a large number
of new victims
in the past half a month?
Someone hopes for the disaster
brought by such Evil Pills to continue.
It seems
a new Sword Master of the Sword Alliance
needs to be elected quickly.
I was truly in a rush before,
but now I'm not.
Why?
You're already back.
What's there to worry about?
Me?
Come on.
Now, everyone knows
Mr. Tang has escaped death
and regained his martial strength.
On Mount Cloud,
in terms of reputation, prestige,
wisdom, talent, and...
Let's skip that part.
I did declare to enter the election,
but in fact,
you and I are both aware
that I'm not suited to be
the leader of a righteous sect.
Besides,
you are completely altruistic,
while I...
am totally different.
You have personal agendas.
That makes you an even better fit
for the position of Sword Master.
Otherwise, how are you going to
abuse public power for personal gain?
I don't need the Sword Alliance
to help me with my personal affairs.
How am I aching again?
I'd better go meet
Senior Shui Duopo now
for another acupuncture treatment.
Mr. Tang.
Mr. Tang,
drink the tea now.
Put your heart and soul into the election.
Master Shao.
What an old weasel.
These Fengliu Shop disciples'
bodies
should be fed to dogs!
Miss Xifang, how kind of you
to bury them all.
Piled-up corpses could cause a plague.
They must be properly disposed of.
Hey, you!
Just dump the body there.
That's about right.
Thank you for the hard work,
Master Shangguan.
I've heard that the poison pills
have made a particularly fierce comeback.
God knows what's going on.
Right after the ferocious battle,
an enormous number
of Evil Pills suddenly appeared
in jianghu again.
Thankfully, the visionary Master Shao
has ordered a search
for villains at large,
and those secretly taking Evil Pills
to be detained.
Also, we're fortunate
to have your instructions
on the drug crackdown.
You've taught us how to
break up Fengliu Shop strongholds
and deal with those afflicted by poison.
Otherwise,
we rough fellows
would be completely lost.
Unfortunately,
some people are still picking on me,
since I once worked for Fengliu Shop.
Your contributions to the Sword Alliance
are evident to all.
Even commoners are saying
you're a heroine of justice.
Just ignore those remarks
made out of jealousy.
If I become Sword Master,
I'll not only eliminate all poison pills
within half a year,
but also distribute the gold
of Fengliu Shop
to all the elders and disciples
who fought hard
in the battle.
Is that true?
Of course.
Mr. Tang brought 100,000 taels of gold in
when he joined the Sword Alliance.
I certainly
need to make a gesture too.
Hold on.
Are you trying to bribe me?
Don't read too much into that,
Master Shangguan.
Whether I can be Sword Master or not,
I'll serve the Sword Alliance
wholeheartedly.
It's getting dark.
Why don't you bring the disciples back,
Master Shangguan?
I'm going to pay a visit to Mr. Tang.
How nice of you, Miss Xifang.
Even such exhausting work in the daytime
can't stop you from visiting Mr. Tang
at night.
What a devoted member you are.
I'm only atoning for my sins.
Okay.
Brothers, finish up quickly.
We're going home!
On my way back from down the mountain
just now,
I saw these poisoned people
suddenly assault others.
I've had those poisoned
yet living individuals detained.
These people were from jianghu.
It was the Evil Pills
that took their lives.
Some ate too many Evil Pills
and died when the toxins kicked in.
Others were attacked and killed
by pill takers.
When the bodies
over here were found,
they were far from each other.
It proves there has been
a large-scale outbreak of toxicity.
Black Tuli has been stolen.
These wounds were caused
by the Moon-crossing Ring.
Did Chi Yun encounter these people?
Chi Yun has been gone for a long time.
Even Shen Langhun can't find him.
Is he in trouble now?
Oh, right.
Perhaps
the Soul-seeking Technique
of Tianren Realm can help.
Even this technique
can't locate Chi Yun.
He must be trapped
somewhere.
Mr. Tang,
can I see you now?
You've come to me
before I go to you.
We finally met again after half a month.
Mr. Tang, I heard
that you had not only recovered,
but also regained
all your martial strength.
It is great news to the Sword Alliance.
My survival through great peril
must be extremely bad news
to you, Miss Xifang.
Now, the poison crisis has risen again.
The Sword Alliance needs
someone who knows
how to properly deal with it.
You're indeed
the best martial fighter in the world.
But when it comes to this matter,
you're not as competent as I am.
How dare you bring this up?
Although Fengliu Shop has collapsed,
there is
a drastic increase in the number of people
affected by the poison pills.
I think you know best
about why,
don't you?
You can't prove it.
Don't throw false accusations, Mr. Tang.
I've brought you some health tonics.
Mr. Tang,
if you don't need them for yourself,
keep them for Mr. Chi,
who has gone missing.
Perhaps they'll be helpful to him.
Mr. Chi has been missing for a long time.
Had better find him soon.
No need for the tonics.
Why did you join the Sword Alliance?
Did Ghostly Peony send you?